{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "category": "math",
      "name": "geometry",
      "description": "Some simple questions about the number of sides on polygons.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "front": "How many sides on a triangle?",
          "back": "3",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "How many sides on a rectangle?",
          "back": "4",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "How many sides on a line?",
          "back": "2, maybe.",
          "star": false
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "category": "science",
      "name": "planets",
      "description": "One question for each of the eight (sorry Pluto) planets in our solar system.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "front": "A runaway greenhouse effect has made this planet unimaginably hot. It's known as Earth's sister planet.",
          "back": "Venus",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "This planet is closest to the sun, and is named after the messenger of the Olympians.",
          "back": "Mercury",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "We live here.",
          "back": "Earth",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "This planet is red and boasts the largest mountain in the solar system.",
          "back": "Mars",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "The largest planet, featuring a storm that's thrice the size of Earth and a 200-year-old stormy red dot.",
          "back": "Jupiter",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "This planet's enormous rings are 99% of why people like it so much.",
          "back": "Saturn",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "This planet is blue, featuers a small ring, and is essentially sideways.",
          "back": "Uranus",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "The farthest planet from the Sun, named after the Roman god of the sea (also the god of horses, believe it or not).",
          "back": "Neptune",
          "star": false
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "category": "video games",
      "name": "minecraft blocks",
      "description": "A handful of blocks from Minecraft. The correct answers are the ways to obtain these blocks in survival mode.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "front": "How do I get a block of diamond ore?",
          "back": "Mine diamond ore with a silk touch pickaxe",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "What do I need to craft an enchanting table?",
          "back": "Four obsidian, two diamonds, and a book.",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "How do I craft diorite? I can mine it naturally, sure, but that's not important right now!",
          "back": "Two cobblestone and two pieces of quartz",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "How can I get gilded blackstone?",
          "back": "Mine it with silk touch from a bastion in the nether.",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "Where can I find wet sponge?",
          "back": "In an ocean monument, although sometimes they can generate without it.",
          "star": false
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "category": "video games",
      "name": "spelunky 2 worlds",
      "description": "Definitely not as popular as Minecraft, but I love this game a ton! These questions will present a fact or something, and ask for the relevant in-game location.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "front": "I'm a horned lizard. Excluding the Cosmic Ocean, where am I?",
          "back": "Dwelling",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "I'm Osiris. Where am I?",
          "back": "Duat",
          "star": false
        },
        {
          "front": "I'm a proto-shopkeeper. Where am I?",
          "back": "Mothership",
          "star": false
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "metadata": [
    {
      "recentIds": [
        "4",
        "2",
        "3"
      ],
      "currentId": "4",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "defaults": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "light-mode": true,
      "front-side-first": true,
      "shuffled": true,
      "starred-only": true
    }
  ]
}